GRCO ANDRIC

288 Alexander Fontein, Discobolos, Kimberley, NC 8321 | H: 053-830-3147 | C: 083-454-0905 | grco.anel@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I am a Proud Officer in the South African National Defense Force. I am a goal orientated person that believe to lead from the front. I am a team player with 21 years of people management experience. I am a firm believer in getting the best possible outputs with the least amount of inputs. There is nothing that can not be accomplished. As an Officer i have learnt to be Flexible in every task that is given to me.

QUALIFICATIONS

- Training and development
- Quick learner
- Results/Goal-oriented
- Microsoft Office

- Operations/people management
- Excel in Transport Fleet Management
- Reports generation and analysis
- Client-focused

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- I wrote an accident prevention plan for Fleet managers that was adopted and implemented in the South African National Defense Force.
- Our transport section was indicated as the best managed transport for three years in a row.
- When i was the Fixed Assets Manager in Kwa Zulu Natal (KZN) i managed the closing down of 10 Reserve Force Units and 3 Military units on my own.
- I was the Project Manager on the Military side with the revamp of the Officers and NCO Mess at Ladysmith Military Base.
- I represented the Province for 3 years in Practical Shooting (IPSC) at the SANDF Championships.
- In 2017 i participated in the Fittest Soldier Competition on SANDF level and also received a reward for endurance.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

01/2017 to Current Training and Range Safety Officer

S A N D F (South African National Defence Force) — Kimberly, NC I am the Training Officer of the unit. Make sure in post training programs are relevant and carried out professionally. Range Safety is one of my main responsibilities. Implementing shooting and training programs in a safe manner and to ensure that training facilities are up to standard and safe for use. i give musketry coaching to about 500 members a year.

12/2006 to 01/2017 TRANSPORT FLEET MANAGER

S A N D F (South African National Defense Force) — Kimberly, NC

I Managed a fleet of 200 military vehicles. From Routing and scheduling to routine maintenance programs. One of my biggest achievements was to maintain a 94% serviceability on my fleet for about 5 years. I revised transport policies and wrote plans that was implemented in the military.

12/2003 to 12/2006

Fixed Assets Manager SANDF — Ladysmith, KZN

Managed all Military Fixed Assets in the whole Natal Province. This included all infrastructure in all Military units at that time. I managed all lease agreements with local Municipalities and other organisations. I was responsible for maintenance and upgrading programs regarding infrastructure. I managed all Contractors and made sure that they comply to all OHS regulations. I did the budget planning and made sure we managed our allocated budget effectively

EDUCATION AND PROFESSIONAL TRAINING

2014

3 Year Diploma: Road Transport Fleet Management

 $\label{lem:conditional} \mbox{University of Johannesburg, Bunting Road Campus-Johannesburg, GP, South}$

Africa

All aspects of running a successful Transport Operation. Routing and Scheduling, Transport Economics, Maintenance, Rules and National Regulations. How to manage resources to reach best possible results. All modules can be given on request.

Officer Level

2006

Certificate: Fundamentals of Project Management

Damelin - Ladysmith KZN — Ladysmith, KZN, South Africa

Basic principals to Project Management. All the steps to be taken. How to manage a Project.

Officer Level: Military Courses

Infantry School Oudtshoorn, Center Of Excellance - Lohathlha, Army Gymnasium

- Heidelburg South Afri - Oudtshoorn, Lohathlha, Heidelburg South Africa

MILITARY COURCES

01 Basic Training SA Army Gymnasium

02 Platoon Weapons SA Army Gymnasium

03 Section Leading SA Army Gymnasium

04 Officers Formative SA Army Gymnasium

05 Method of Instruction SA Army Gymnasium

06 Assistant Physical Training Instructor SA Army Gymnasium

07 Infantry 1 SA Army Infantry School

08 Infantry 2 SA Army Infantry School

09 Chemical and Biological Warfare Instructors 7 Medical Battalion Group 10

Mortar Specialist SA Army Infantry School

11 Coy 2IC SA Army Infantry School

12 Coy Commander SA Army Infantry School

13 Sub Unit Commanders CTC Lohathlha

LANGUAGES

English: Speak, Read and Write Good

PERSONAL INFORMATION

DATE OF BIRTH: 12 JUNE 1977

MARITAL STATUS: MARRIED TO ANEL ANDRIC

DEPENDENTS: MARKO ANDRIC

DANIEL ANDRIC
RUBEN ANDRIC

PERSONAL INFO CAN BE REQUESTED